Contact

bolanosandres43@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/andres-bolanos-dev (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Node.js NestJS

Angular

Andres Bolaños

Software Developer specializing in Angular, NodeJS, and TypeScript Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Summary

I'm a Web Developer with experience in creating dynamic, optimized web applications. Expert in technologies such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, Node.js, API development. A creative person who enjoys designing efficient solutions, familiar with agile methodologies and development environments.

Experience

Talent.com
Desarrollador web
July 2022 - May 2023 (11 months)
Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Creation of algorithms for information extraction (web scraping) using JavaScript.

Maintenance and optimization for problem prevention.

Agile methodologies.

Ekisa Ltda

Desarrollador de software

June 2020 - June 2022 (2 years 1 month)

Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Developed user interfaces using HTML, CSS, TypeScript, and the Angular framework.

Requirements analysis and API consumption.

User interface design.

Version control with Git.

Agile methodologies (SCRUM/DevOps) implementation.

Education

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA)

Técnico en Programación de Software, Desarrollo de aplicaciones
web · (October 2019 - December 2020)